# MAURICE MORGAN

16300 W 123rd St. Olathe, Kansas 66062 . (316) 304-4388 . modcox2@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Returning non-traditional University of Kansas student in 2nd year of Computer Science curriculum with a 3.07 cumulative GPA expecting to graduate Dec. 2024. Former bar professional with 10+ years experience successfully managing clients, projects, employees/personnel, and sensitive information/resources. Proven track record for exceeding prescribed KPIs.

#### **EDUCATION**

Wichita East High School; International Baccalaureate (IB) Diploma
The University of Kansas; Computer Science: Cumulative GPA: 3.07

Relevant Coursework: Programming II (Python), Embedded Systems, Discrete Structures

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Account & Distribution Specialist - Black Labs Craft Meadery; Olathe, KS May 2021 - Aug 2022

- Managed 2 wholesale accounts in Lawrence, KS, and 5 in the Greater Kansas City area.
- Opened 4 new accounts since May 2021 surpassed 1 acquisition per quarter KPI.
- Managed retail space and storefront for 100% of the operation hours.

Licensed Insurance Sales Agent - SelectQuote, Inc.; Overland Park, KS Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

- Licensed Life and Health Insurance Producer in 16 states.
- Collected and secured sensitive PHI/PII on CRM software compliant with federal law and Medicare regulations.
- Identified health needs of clients to pitch and sell an encompassing plan during a first-time 30 min to 1-hour phone call.

Bar Manager - Restaurant, Pub & Games; Lawrence, KS

June 2019 - Aug 2020

- Maintained professional working relationships with vendors, beverage distribution representatives, and local manufacturers.
- Coordinated FOH staff and prepared FOH schedule kept bar labor costs under 2% of weekly bar revenue for 10 consecutive months.
- Controlled bar inventory value of standing inventory and weekly purchases were < 20% of weekly bar revenue.

Housing Director - Richmond Property Group/ATO Fraternity; Lawrence, KS July 2018 - Aug 2019

- Supervised the property, grounds, staff, and 60 live-in undergraduate fraternity members.
- Lacking a budget from RPG, fundraised with Parent's Club and chapter alumni to renovate property structures.
- Maintained professional working relationships with vendors, technicians, University of Kansas faculty, and Housing Directors of other SFL Greek-affiliated organizations.

### SKILLSETS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Inventory Management purchasing, packaging, product analysis, cost negotiation
- Programming Windows and Linux CLI, Python, C++, C
- **Project Management** Event planning, end-to-end management of resources, conflict resolution, fundraising, property management, human resource management
- Language Proficiency Basic French, Basic Japanese, and Basic American Sign Language

## **REFERENCES**

Carl Hinchey Owner/Operator Big Rip Brewing Co. (303)903-3205 carl@bigripbrewing.com

Daniel Luckey Owner Restaurant, Pub and Games (785) 979-7588 dan@rpglawrence.com

Bryne Gonzales, Au.D. Audiologist NuSound Hearing (785) 640-4823 brynepgonzales@gmail.com

Emily Peterson Proprietor/Operator Merchants Pub & Plate (785) 843-4111 emily@merchantsonmass.com